OK we are all set.  So if you are a fan of One All One
T Make Some Noise
and if you are a fan of S Diamonds Make Some
Noise,
well there's a little bit of sound from the East.  It has
also come from the West.  East and West cricket is the
best.  let start.  In the count of five four three
to one game on.
Mr. Puneet is on strike.
Oh good bowling.  A beauty of a delivery
from Suraj Rao.   You have made a
good start.  Starting with a dot
ball,
power play on
and this is a brilliant shot in the air.  If the
fielder is present at a
long distance, then one run is scored in one throw.
If you are very fast then
you can easily take these two runs.
Puneet completed two runs with ease.
Good running between the wickets.
This time the ball has been blown into the air.
And I could
n't balance myself a little here and there.
Because of this the ball slipped from his hand.   It is
very difficult to catch a catch like Arabi.   Yes of course.
Very nice shot here.  Puneet is a very aggressive
batsman here.
Ok.  We have must most awaited.
Mr. Sunny Bhardwaj on strike.
He batted very well last year.  He is a
good aggressive batsman.
He always has an all-round performance
in bowling and batting, but
this time see, he has bowled well, Suraj
Rao has impressed the new batsman a bit as well,
no run on the first ball, five
runs on four balls,
one or two balls, it seems he will take some time to settle down,
this time good bowling
and the appeal for wide was rejected by the umpire here.
His decision will be the final decision above all of us umpires.
Here only the umpire's decision will prevail.
Five balls, five runs, excellent start
by Edge Diamonds here.
This time it made space.
Awesome shot here in the covers.
Four runs.  This is what I was saying Mitesh ji,
when the power play is going on, the batsman
should go for technical shots and a
proper cover drive was seen here.
Absolutely excellent shot, very good shot,
well driven into the covers, the bat was the brush
and the outfield was a canvas, beats the
fielder in the covers and four runs, one was gone nine
for no one, one team,
it was a proper cricketing shot, I would say yes, it
definitely reminds me of the way Virat
Kohli, Rahul Dravid, VVS Laxman used to
bat in that era
and they won a good match for India,
which used to be One Day International at that time, if we
talk about 90, 200, then yes, this is
exactly the
speciality of an experienced batsman,
he believes more in technical shots
rather than fancy
and here, batting at a run rate of nine,
one l one team, yes, has made a
good start, a fielder is
stationed here at deep mid wicket, it is very wide
and the keeper has missed here.  Is it
five wides?  Are these five whites?
Absolutely, the
strike rate which was nine has become
14 here.  Absolutely.
So that's a free bet is given by S
Diamonds to one l one team bonus five runs
looking to play for the big one understand wow
good comeback from Sumit Sh just a single run this
time this time proper elevation was not found could
not time it
and the car will move forward with one run we have
seen good bounce here the bowlers are
trying to hit a shot
but a wide ball will be given here
umpire's decision is the decision please
16 for no loss
hit here there could have been a chance of run out that went
for bye there is a faded delivery from
Sumit Sh
17 for no loss
oh here Sumit Sh is a little balanced
there in the run up but he says
okay we will continue Bing
ji absolutely just some time back Ardeep
Singh also bowled six wides in an over the
record is the highest Jacobram 13
wides in one over it
was a match one day international
we have some time limit so I
hope it should be done in over time
absolutely right
this time demand for two excellent hits  There is a
lot of demand from the one l one team dug out, it will
definitely happen here and it should happen because there are spectators,
supporters, there will be
demand, this support is needed, we are
totally beaten and once again excellent bowling
and another appeal for wide here,
keeping the ball far away from the batsman's eyes,
not on his bat, keeping it a little away
and this is what he is doing right,
Sumit Sh made a little comeback in this over, if
you also see the length then he is bowling at a very good length,
see this and once he got deceived, excellent
bowling,
proper good length bowling,
10 runs came here, in the previous over nine runs came,
19 runs no wicket,
last ball coming up
and the over ends with a dot ball, two was gone
19 for none, all one team
and the match progressed at a very good pace.
19 runs in two overs here.  The last over was quite
exciting.  Either it was a wide ball
or it was very good bowling.
What a party,
Arpit ji, if any team wins the match,
we are definitely going to get lemon juice or orange juice,
one of the two, the
canal has started right here, Amol Thakur,
only a single,
quite a century bowling here.   The
score card is slowly moving forward and the
batsman is completely dancing
on the crease.  The way bowling is being done here by
Edge Diamonds.  Now this
series of power plays is over.  You can see
four fielders standing at extra cover
point, one fielder at third man,
his team came here with complete planning
and this batsman changed his shot and a good shot here,
fielder present there
and this demand of two, will two runs be completed
and these two runs are completed here, very
poor fielding performance here, S
misses a simple run out chance,
wants to hit a little directly, wicket could have been taken,
two runs will be taken in the form of run out here, Sunny
22, no wicket
and this shot in the air, away from the fielder present here,
and capitalizes with two runs, good running
between the wickets from Sunny and Punit,
they say in sales language, converting
inquiries into sales,
not one run, they are taking two runs, so
directly sales are
closing one.
Whenever we get a lead, it becomes a sale either
close one or close loss.
Yes, yes, it is our job to convert leads.   At
present, we have to see who will take the lead
in this match.  Excellent over here
by Amol Thakur.  Only five runs have been given
in five balls.  Good affordable Bing key.  I have
played this time.  The ball is going towards third man.   The
fielder made a great effort but the ball went
out of the boundary line for four runs.
And what is this, being a batsman,
as I told you in the morning.
Make some noise for Mr. Sunny Bhardwaj.
Whatever he has done for the team, he has done a
great job.
As I told you in the morning, quite like
sometimes in IPL also we have seen that
if many batsmen feel that they are
not doing well in that match then they give their wicket to the team
and it is becoming quite interesting.  The Big Bash
League (WPL) is currently underway.  ISPL is also
becoming very interesting.  And the best
over of IPL is the swing over.
So a lot of cricket will be seen here.
Then after that IPL is yet to come.   Yes of course.   There will be a
lot of cricketing in the coming four
months.
ISPL swing ball is called over which
tape is applied and it is a proper swing.
Banana in swing like ball.  So
we got to see some very interesting matches
in the last few days.  Get one here for three overs 28.  We will
take only one run here.
This time you can see the outside edge that
both the batsmen are trying to play across the line.
If you hit a little on the off side then
you will get runs. The
score is currently on 30.
Look, the bowling is going in the excellent block hole
and we are going for two runs.  There could have been a danger
but I ran two runs quickly.
Very good running here.
And why did Dogesh Bhai suddenly come here in
between?  He also has to run between the wickets.
So to Rans Taken 32 for one some
fun moments in Fatima Grounds.
Only a single, good stop,
very good performance of the batting, I would say here, they are
not giving any chance of any shot
here, yes, the same
here, S Diamonds will try their best,
now
kept it at a distance, see from the batsman's eyes,
wanted to come and play across the line, got
totally beaten, so only five runs were given
in this over and four overs, 33 for one, one l one
team,
as they had said in the toss, they will
restrict it to 35.  Sunny sir was saying
that we will make 70.  The captain here
is S Diamonds,
both of his predictions were wrong,
but he
says that now the game of cricket can
turn the tables at any time.
Yes, absolutely,
sometimes happiness, sometimes sadness and in a moment,
Masha.
Very good bowling here, totally beating the
batsman, so
Arpit ji, the way the game was played today, it does
not seem at all that both the
teams have made a good effort.
Yes, in the beginning it seemed that 19 runs were scored in two overs,
after that the game has slowed down a lot
here,
this time two runs outside edge in the third man area,
but the fielder fumbled a bit
and see, he is
running for 30 runs and will get
three runs,
three runs, excellent running between the
wickets.
One One team also has to be appreciated.  If he is
not getting single boundaries, then
he is scoring runs by running as much as he gets time.  I am
not leaving any chance here at all.   Yes of course.
And another batsman coming back.
They say, whatever we
got, we got it,
thunder of applause, one and one
team out here.   It has
blown away.  wonderful shot.  The
batsman will take two runs here as the fielder is present there.  Two runs
taken here,
batsman name please.  Batsman name please
Sudhanshu.  Thank you very much.
I think after Sudhanshu ji is out,
Himanshu ji should now come to bat.  So
Himanshu ji has been kept in reserve for the next match.
[laughter]
Stamina was
reserved for the final.  Is stamina.
Direct Grand Finale What a thing.
Excellent shot, four runs,
powerful, brilliant.   Give it for
42.  Now the last two balls.
Did Arpit cross the 50 mark,
keeping the expression of 50, One
Il1 team
and look, the
ball is in the air, we will catch it here, wicket
keeper had made a
great effort, was going for a big hit
but the fielder was there at long on
and took a great catch, that's a third wicket fall
of One Il One team, but really good performance
from both the teams, S Diamonds and One Il
One team, the
direction in which the shot was hit is the longest
part of the field, keep this in mind also,
good capture again by Amol at long on,
Sridhar has
pulled the last ball, short pitch ball
and has made the ball go
for four runs.  46 for
three after five overs good performance
from the team one l one team s Diamonds one
the toileted to field first and wow good
batting.
So 47 to win
and for the next match I request the
two teams for the coin toss
I request
ok I will have to wait a bit
for the toss match one loser vs match two loser
so Arpit ji the first match unison
superstar vs the one who will lose the match
ji absolutely the first innings
went quite well here S also bowled very well
and went up and down a lot
and joining in the com box suddenly tatkal
ticket mister finish this match in 10 minutes
please fielders please go for the bowling the
match has to be finished in 10 minutes your time
starts now
and here with complete planning Orange
Army one l one team coming into fielding
yes the DRM is over
47 to win who is going to
bowl the first over
S Diamonds the
stalwart batsman has arrived these
S Diamonds the opening pair
S Sep come.
Setting the fielding here, Mr. Sunny Bhardwaj, there will be
two fielders outside the 30 art circle and
one fielder
in the mid wicket area,
ok.  Okay so once again welcome back to the
biggest rivalry of the evening ICICI
Lombard presents Brokers Premier League
I welcome once again all the viewers
spectated ass myself Mithya Solanki
in the com box Arpit
number
and here taking a lot of time
and here taking a lot of time one L1 team
setting its fielding
yes absolutely Himanshi ji said that the
match has to be finished in 10 minutes
and then everyone will go for lemon juice or orange juice
party.   Yes,
we are definitely waiting for that.
Absolutely
Aniruddha wherever orange juice is required.
OK we all set Sudarshan Sreedharan on
strike.  Suraj non strike imitation here we
go three to one game on.
This time he wanted to push.  Knowing there was no fielder towards third man, he
wanted to play a cut shot.  But there was no contact between
bat and ball.   It was
good that there was no contact because the
wicketkeeper had dropped the ball.
V Sudarshan and Suraj double ace
on the crease.
And once the best Bing from Prashant.   The
target of 47 is a good total given here. The
One L1 team has
bowled well so far.
Two balls were bowled very accurately at a
good length. The bowler is not taking time to get
set. It could have been a
close call but he
ran quickly for a run. He just guided the
ball but it took a heavy edge. He was
lucky that the ball did not go into anyone's hands and
went away. Very good
bowling. This is a good start here. The number 14
jersey brings to mind only one player,
Ricky Ponting, the aggressive
Australian captain. This time the fielder has taken the catch and not over the fielder. A
brilliant catch by Akash.
Generally, we have seen such catches being dropped
in previous matches. This time there was
no mistake at all by the One L1 team.
You can see that the first wicket fell. A proper
judgement was made. He went a little back and ran a little
back and caught it with ease. The
first wicket fell. Good capture again by
Akash. Suraj Rao departs after four balls
being bowled. It's one for one.
Coming on strike,
only one run and one wicket was lost in four balls. He
pushed it lightly here.  The shot will be taken if the third man
fielder is present there and we will take one run, so we do
n't want to take any risk here. We have to
protect the wickets in the first over and I
think we will start the fireworks in the second over.
Now, it is
definitely the power play, so we have to take advantage,
but we will have to keep the wickets under control.
Here, we
will bowl the last ball of this over, Prashant to
Sudarshan, wanted to cut, but got beaten.
Excellent start from Prashant, only two runs
and one wicket
and four overs left, 45 to get.
45 runs needed in four overs. We
will talk about the required run rate per over,
Arpit ji, 11.25.
If these two overs are economical for Team One, then the
match will be in their hands. Yes, that is
exactly what I was going to say, which was
required earlier for nine, which
you can see before the start of the match, after one over, it
went straight to 11. And the new bowler
here, Mr. Puneet, seems to be quite experienced.
Yes, experience influences the candidate a bit
and this is what we have seen
in some matches, the way we run up and
look at this, he has bowled a great ball this time, there is a
fielder present there.  Will take the wicket
Keepan has
taken the wicket on the first ball, it is amazing, the
cricket of One L One team, a
very wonderful sight of fielding,
giving a statement by One L One team,
One L One team in fielding
and a very first ball, Puneet on the money,
good bowling,
excellent performance here, both the teams are becoming
very interesting, the
heartbeats get faster and the breath stops.   The
weather is
pleasant.  It becomes very exciting.
And one more thing they say is that cricket is not a game.  There
is a festival.  It's carnival.  It is
celebrated like a festival.
Uday Mandavkar is the new batsman.
One run will be taken here on the first ball.
Look at the pressure.
Above the Edge Diamonds is perfectly maintained by the
One L One team here.
Yes, absolutely, other teams would also be watching the excellent
bowling and fielding performance of the One L One team.   The
ball went far away from the keeper.
Going to backward regions.  We will stop it
and take two runs.
I think now between Sudarshan and Uday, he
says, one of them should
take the responsibility of resiliency, now to hit the big heads,
yes definitely one of the
batsmen will have to go on a big scale, only there are
three deliveries
left in this over of the power play, also
or only single digit score is five for
two, this time he has played a powerful attack
and a great stop, see the throw there too,
by Prashant,
somewhere three runs are left for the team.
Only the four has been saved.
Yes, of course, what would you say
about fielding, you have
not seen any fielding till now, here he reminded me of Jonty Rhodes.
Six pe two
this time a strong hit track could have been a chance there.   I'll
take one run here.
From for to still single digit on the
board.  Arpit ji, the
required rate is increasing here, right
here it is 12, now close to 13,
this time the ball has been blown, the ball will go away and will
stick in the hands of the fielder, it
seemed here that the ball will go into the constellation,
but no, the
ball got
stuck in the hands of the fielder here and with the fall of the third wicket,
S Diamonds have gone 7 for three and
need 40 runs in three overs.
Yes, the first ball that I got to see was the
replay of the first ball in the last ball.
Correct.
Now the
series of fielding restoration ended here.
Maximum fielders can go outside the
circle.  But they say that it
is mandatory to have a minimum of four fielders.  Inside Circle.   There
are many all-rounders in the One L One team like
Mr. Puneet, we got to see very good performance in batting and bowling
and now we will come back to bowling, field
arrangement deep backward square leg deep
mid wicket one fielder cow corner one at deep
point long off long
on sh third man sh cover leg
fielder square leg feels it is behind the stumps
no there is
fine leg fielder.  Now the fine leg has been
brought here.  Fine leg and square leg and
deep mid wicket fielders.
What is your prediction for this over?
Now it seems that he will definitely take a wicket in this over.
There was a chance with the ball in the air but it
remained very far away from Puneet.
But he says he will play safe.  Will
not give much fuss.
Demand for at least two wickets out here
in this over.
Yes, absolutely, one and one team, all the supporters here are
definitely looking for wickets, take the full toss
ball, I have hit it well, the
fielder is present there, as long as I throw it, I will
complete two runs easily, two
runs taken is a
bit difficult, Arpit ji, 14 runs
per over,
ji, not many attempts are being seen
here because very tight
bowling is being done here by the one and one team.
Absolutely look into the block hole
once again will they go for two runs they are going
for two runs
oh that's
not expected sunny that bounce
uneven bounce from over his head but the
backup fielder is very important
12 pe three 35 needed in 15 balls he is
tracking himself perfectly here,
sweeping and see this could be a run out chance.
Reached
33 runs in 14 balls, very tight
bowling here.  You can see him
bowling straight into the block hole.  They are
not giving any chance to the
batsman at all.  We have to make do with singles and doubles
but singles and doubles will
not suffice here, the huge score that the
team has made here, in the
last ball of the over
only
nine runs from this over
and here while trying to pick the second run,
another wicket fell, there was no need for the
second run but in order to increase the requirement, the
S team took a chance here and the
wicket fell
and here after three overs,
four wickets for 16 runs, it seems quite difficult,
for this this match will have to be seen now,
by what margin will the One L One team want to win this match,
thanks
Prashant coming to bowl
and here another run out, a wonderful
view of wicket keeping by Bhesh.
We are seeing two consecutive run outs here.
And shot in the air, fielder present here, very
brilliant attempt by
Amit,
very good effort by Amit, there was a
chance of run out here and this continued
four
and here due to misfielding he was
not able to hit four, so he scored four runs by running
here
and brilliant shot, fielder present there
and on top of that backup fielder was also present there.
End of the over: 23 runs after four overs.
Only 23 runs needed in one over.   It
seems that the 35-run restriction that S had
decided to impose has been achieved in his batting.
And in the last over,
Amit sets the run-up here, he is a
very experienced bowler.  I
play in many leagues in different leagues of Bombay.
And as we were just talking this morning,
we saw another jersey number seven here.
And one more spin bowler is seen,
very few spin options are available
since morning, we have got
one more edition in that spin
ICC Luba Broker Premier League,
very brilliant bowling here, completely deceiving the
batsman, making the
batsman dance on the race, the way he is
bowling.
This is the speciality of left arm spin.
And along with the batsman, the wicketkeeper is also getting
deceived here.   The
keeper was
going for a little run out there, but he was going to have a conversation.  The
event was already over.   There were a
lot of run outs and a lot of runs were already scored
in the innings.
That's a formality of the last four balls.
Oh that's MSD for you behind the stumps.
MSD on Bing MA Keeping.
Seven number jersey Thala for Region.  There
are plates everywhere.   This is a
wonderful sight of wicketkeeping.
Not giving any chance to the batsman here.
Bhesh the wicket keeper stump
good stumping and three balls left
and the first match will be win for the team
One L One team
if you have noticed one thing there are many all-
rounders in One L One team there are
many bowling bats batting options available
here so I
think Arpit ji we should also get a chance to
play in One L One team yes
of course if we have that much talent then
we will definitely get a chance
so we are ready for the application form
sh pitch ball I have played it in the direction of square leg
and only one run will be scored I think we are
going for two runs so
let's run two runs here.  Excellent
running.  Now, by what margin this match is
lost is also important.  There will not be a big defeat.  We will do
something to increase the price here.   I would
like to control the net here.
Absolutely.
Two balls left.  21 runs
and clean bowled
cut and bowled.  Brilliant bowling
here by Amit.
Looks like the One L One team has found its Shane One.
Exactly here,
so one ball left and one one all one team,
you were talking that we should also get a chance
in one all one team.  I have been
filling the form for three years.  Haven't got a chance yet.
Yes, my form got rejected.
ok one ball left it
is not easy to get into the top 11 whoever you are
seeing here are all talented players
absolutely correct answer
and that's it that's the end of the match make some
noise for the team one I will one team
very brilliant bowling performance here